Guide to the National Guardian Photographs PHOTOS.213
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Honduras, 1957-1987 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Honduras, 1969-1989 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Jamaica, 1969-1989 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Panama, 1966-1981 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Paraguay, 1958-1974 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Peru, 1957-1962 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Trinidad, 1956-1989 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Uruguay, 1963-1985 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Venezuela, 1971-1985 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Mexico, 1963-1974 (Box 96, Folder 9-12)
- Mexico, 1964-1989 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Mozambique, 1964-1989 (Box 97, Folder 2-5)
- Philippines, 1965-1989 (Box 97, Folder 6-7)
- Philippines, 1970-1986 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Philippines, 1956-1978 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Nicaragua, 1956-1978 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Nicaragua – Army, 1933-1990 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Nicaragua – Contras, 1980-1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Nicaragua – Education, 1983-1986 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Nic Election, 1983-1986 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Nicaragua – General Life in, 1984-1984 (Box 98, Folder 42924)
- Nicaragua Solidarity, 1979-1986 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Nicaragua: Health, 1984-1989 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Nicaragua – Miskitos, 1981-1988 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Obando y Bravo Archbishop of Nicaragua, 1985-1989 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Daniel Ortega, 1984-1988 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Nicaragua/ Religion, 1984-1987 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Nicaragua – Personages, 1983-1989 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Left Strategy, 1983-1989 (Box 99, Folder 6-7)
- Nica – Opposition, 1955-1987 (Box 99, Folder 8-9)
- Nicaragua – War Pix, 1984-1988 (Box 99, Folder 10-11)
- South Africa (old), 1983-1986 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Malaysia, 1958-1986 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Micronesia, 1959-1975 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- New Caledonia, 1981-1981 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Papua New Guinea, 1985-1985 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Thailand, 1983-1983 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Thailand, 1984-1984 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Taiwan, 1951-1976 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Laos, 1958-1971 (Box 100, Folder 8-13)
- Laos, 1959-1986 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- DPRK –North Korea, 1959-1986 (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
- Korea – 1940s-1950s, 1958-1975 (Box 101, Folder 4-5)
- Personalities – South Korea, 1940-1959 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Personalities – North Korea, 1952-1972 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- South Korea, 1965-1979 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- U.S. Demonstrations – Korea, 1960-1979 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Korean War, 1973-1976 (Box 101, Folder 10-11)
- Korean War, 1947-1972 (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
- Indonesia, 1947-1972 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Japan, 1948-1974 (Box 102, Folder 4-6)
- Kampuchea, 1941-1983 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Korea – Negotiations/ Panmunjom, 1982-1988 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- South Korea, 1951-1957 (Box 102, Folder 9-10)
- DPRK – North Korea, 1949-1985 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
- Burma, 1953-1977 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Banding Peace Conference, 1954-1966 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Anna Louise Strong, 1955-1963 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- China and other Countries (visits etc.), 1955-1959 (Box 103, Folder 42893)
- China-Oversized Photos-Misc., 1949-1976 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- China: Party, Diplomats, etc., 1972-1972 (Box 103, Folder 42988)
- China – Mao, 1955-1973 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Tibet, 1953-1976 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Mongolia – Outer, 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Agriculture – China, 1961-1965 (Box 104, Folder 3-5)
- Forestry – China, 1944-1976 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- China – Women, 1956-1975 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- China – Minorities, 1974-1974 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- China – Army/Militia, 1973-1974 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- China – Industry, 1972-1976 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- China – Agriculture, 1959-1976 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- China – Education, 1974-1976 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- China – Art/Culture, 1974-1976 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- China – Leadership, 1974-1974 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- China – Medicine, 1971-1976 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- China – Sports, 1974-1974 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- China Miscellaneous, 1974-1974 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- China – Children, 1967-1976 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- China – Current, 1976-1976 (Box 104, Folder 19)
- Guam, 1949-1977 (Box 104, Folder 20)
- Hong Kong, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 21)
- Israel After 1973 War, 1949-1975 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Egypt After 1973, 1973-1975 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Egypt – Between 1967 and 1973 Wars, 1973-1986 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Egypt Before 1967, 1969-1973 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Saudi Arabia, 1956-1964 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Afghanistan, 1949-1975 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Cyprus, 1963-1972 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- India, 1956-1975 (Box 105, Folder 8-10)
- Pakistan, 1947-1987 (Box 106, Folder 1-3)
- Nepal, 1959-1972 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Sri Lanka, 1960-1984 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Iraq, 1960-1982 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Rushdie – Iran Scandal, 1958-1988 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Iran-Iraq War, 1989-1989 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Iran, 1983-1988 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Jordan, 1951-1982 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Kuwait, 1956-1970 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Lebanon, 1961-1974 (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Lebanon General, 1974-1986 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Lebanon – Civil War, 1958-1976 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Libya, 1958-1976 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- OPEC, 1972-1972 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Palestinians, 1973-1975 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Palestine Current, 1968-1973 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Palestinians – General Graphics and Pictures, 1969-1979 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Syria, 1967-1976 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Yemen/Aden, 1967-1975 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- United Arab Emirates, 1962-1986 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Bangladesh, 1976-1976 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Middle East, 1971-1975 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Israel – miscellaneous see also Palestine, 1983-1986 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- West Bank/Gaza, 1948-1987 (Box 108, Folder 2-3)
- Palestine – File, 1987-1988 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Mideast – miscellaneous, 1969-1987 (Box 108, Folder 5-6)
- Israel thru 1948 War, 1969-1986 (Box 108, Folder 7-9)
- Israel, 1946-1948 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Mideast war 1967, 1948-1967 (Box 109, Folder 2-3)
- Israel, 1967-1967 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Israel between 1967 and 1973 Wars, 1976-1977 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Mideast War – October 1973, 1968-1974 (Box 109, Folder 6-7)
- John McManus, Abe Weissbrod, 40th anniversary staff group portrait, 1973-1974 (Box 110)